tassimo.com 2016-05-31

# Home

This website is owned and operated by Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. ("we"). At Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd., we recognise that visitors to our site may be concerned about the information they provide to us and how we handle that information.

The Company is located at Horizon, Honey Lane, Hurley, Maidenhead, Berkshire, SL6 6RJ, England. The legal jurisdiction of this site is England and Wales (“Jurisdiction”).

We respect your privacy. This Privacy Policy outlines the information we collect and how we use it. This Policy applies solely to information collected through this Site and not other sources.

**1\. Conditional Use of this Site**

Your access to and use of this Site and its contents (the “Site”) is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy” or “Policy”), and all applicable laws. By accessing and using this Site, you (the “User” or “you”) accept and agree to these without any limitation or qualification.

**2\. Terms of Use**

Your use of this Site is also subject to the Terms of Use posted on this Site (“ [Terms of Use](https://www.tassimo.co.uk/website-terms-of-use/s-1912/;pgid=EE1gS3V9VMJSRp0F2UFsdAwn0000-hWT0Iay;sid=Bdfr96g7rPT69_92-gLmk8cx2F2xi6dkrtWQCvnzT8KgotHBAOU34-v3) ”)

**3\. Information We Collect**

**a) Personally-Identifiable Information**

On our Site, we collect certain personally-identifiable information, such as name, gender, telephone number and e-mail address, about online visitors who choose to register on our Site or participate in our offers and programmes. We don’t require you to register or provide personally-identifiable information to view our site or access much of its content, such as our many delicious recipes. But if you register, you may use certain additional features that allow you to e.g. receive or access your favourite recipes and participate in our interactive communities. Sharing this additional information with us also helps us customise your website experience. In addition, we may use the information you provide us to send you offers and information about Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd., its portfolio of brands and its partners. Here are the ways we collect personally-identifiable information.

**b) Registration**

To take full advantage of our offers, you may choose to register on our site. In the registration process, we sometimes request certain information (such as your contact information and age) so we can provide you with the communications you request, tailor our Site to better meet your needs and customise our contacts with you.

**c) Contests, competitions and promotions**

Our site contains notices of contests, competitions and games that you can enter. We use the information you provide to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you’re a winner).

**d) E-mail**

When you ask us to send you updates, recipes or other content by e-mail, you may provide us with certain information like your e-mail address so we can fulfil your request.

**e) "Contact Us" link**

If you contact us through the " [Contact Us](http://contactus.jdecoffee.com/tassimo-united-kingdom/ "Contact Us") " link on this site, we ask you for information such as your first name, e-mail address, and other information, so we can respond to your questions and comments. You may choose to provide additional information as well.

**f) Shopping**

When you purchase products or services from Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd., we request your billing information so we can fulfil your request. We use your billing information only to send you the items you ordered.

**g) Send to a Friend**

We may give you the opportunity to tell your friends about features or information on our websites. If you take advantage of our ‘Send to a Friend’ option, we ask you for your friend’s and your first name and e-mail addresses to send the information to them that you requested. We don’t keep or use your friend’s e-mail address for any other purpose.

**h) Other site features**

We offer visitors to our Site various features for their enjoyment, which we change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personally-identifiable information (as outlined in section 3(a)), so we can provide you with these features.

**i) Questionnaires and surveys**

We may ask our website visitors and purchasers to complete surveys and opinion polls to provide feedback on activities, attitudes and interests. These surveys help us understand the needs of our visitors and purchasers.

**j) Information collected by automated means**

We may use cookies, web beacons/pixel tags, log files, and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our Site, use of our online services, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements. For example, through these means, we may collect your browser type and operating system, viewed webpages, links that are clicked, IP address, sites visited before coming to our Site, emails we send that you open, forward, or click through to our Site.

You can set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). Note that the opt-out will apply only to the browser that you are using when you elect to opt out of advertising cookies. Without cookies or pixel tags though, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd.’s website features.

Please see section 8 “ [Cookies](https://www.tassimo.co.uk/cookies/s-1864/;pgid=EE1gS3V9VMJSRp0F2UFsdAwn0000-hWT0Iay;sid=Bdfr96g7rPT69_92-gLmk8cx2F2xi6dkrtWQCvnzT8KgotHBAOU34-v3) ” for further information.

**k) Information collected from other sources**

We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators and public databases. This information may include name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and shopping behavior. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products.

**4\. How we use your information**

We may use the information we collect to contact you from time to time. For example, we may (i) send you promotional offers, materials, and other communications and information about Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd., its portfolio of brands and its partners, (ii) respond to your comments or questions, or (iii) contact you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our Site. We also may use the information you provide to contact you for your opinions on Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. products, services or websites. As described in this Privacy Notice, we also use the information we collect about you to improve our Site, products and services, and to deliver content that is customised to your interests. In addition we may use such personal information:

  * to respond to your questions and requests, to provide you with access to certain areas and features and to communicate with you about your activities on this Site;
  * to share it with our Related Parties as required to perform functions on our behalf in connection with the Site (such as delivery of merchandise, administration of the website or promotions or other features on it, marketing, data analysis or customer services). To do so, it may be necessary for us to transmit your personal information to outside the above Jurisdiction, and, where the site is based within the European Economic Area (EEA), to outside the EEA, and you agree to this transfer. Further use or disclosure of the information by them for other purposes is not permitted. To provide you with product information or promotional and other offers from us or our Related Parties;
  * if required by law, regulation or court order;
  * for the purpose of or in connection with legal proceedings or necessary for establishing, defending or exercising legal rights; or
  * in an emergency to protect the health or safety of website users or the general public or in the interests of national security.

Except as provided in herein, we will not provide any of your personal information to any third parties without your specific consent.

**5\. Opt-out and Opt-in**

We may provide you with an “opt in” or “opt-out” mechanism depending on the requirements of the Site’s Jurisdiction and the Site. An “opt-in” mechanism will provide you the opportunity to positively indicate that you would like or do not object to our sending you such further communications and we will not send you any unless you have “opted-in”. An “opt-out” mechanism will provide you the opportunity to indicate that you do not want us to send you such further communications, and if you “opt-out” we will not send you any.

Either way, opting-in or opting-out will be up to you and, in addition, if you do not want us to use your personal information for a particular purpose or disclose it to a third party, you may “opt out” at any time by contacting us as provided below.

Specific opt-outs may also be provided at the point of collection or along with the communications to you.

Please note though, by opting-out, you may not be able to participate in certain activities on our websites.

**6\. Privacy**

We do not sell or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information about our website visitors, except as described here. We do not share your personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your consent.

We may share personally identifiable information among Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. and Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. brands and subsidiaries. We may also share the information with service providers we have retained to perform services on our behalf, such as to help run promotions, fulfil orders and provide customer service. These service providers may have access to personally-identifiable information about our website visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd., but they are not authorised by Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd.’s behalf or to comply with legal requirements. In addition, we may disclose information where we think it’s necessary to investigate or prevent an actual or suspected crime or injury to ourselves or others, if required by law, or in response to a request from law enforcement authorities or other government officials.

We may conduct joint promotions with other companies. We may share with our promotional partners (and their service providers) certain personally-identifiable information as necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share this information with our promotional partners for any other purpose unless you consent to such sharing.

**7\. Links to other websites**

This Site may contain links to other web sites that we do not own or operate. We do not control, recommend or endorse and are not responsible for these sites or their content, products, services or privacy policies. Downloading material from certain sites may risk infringing intellectual property rights or introducing viruses into your system. You should note when you leave this Site and read the privacy policies and terms of these other sites. You should also independently assess the authenticity of any website which appears or claims that it is one of our sites (including those linked to through an email).

**8\. How we protect your information**

The security of personally-identifiable information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorised use, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personally-identifiable information we collect on this Site. However, we cannot guarantee the security of such information. To the fullest extent permitted by law, we disclaim all liability and responsibility for any Damages you may suffer due to any loss, unauthorised access, misuse or alteration of any information you submit to this Site.

**9\. Use of “Cookies” on our websites**

Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. websites do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information about you. However, if you wish to restrict or block the cookies which are set by any of our websites, or indeed any other website, you can do this through your browser settings. The “Help” function within your browser should tell you how to disable this function.

Please be aware that restricting cookies may impact on the functionality of the Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd. websites.

**10\. Updates to this Privacy Policy**

Please note we may change information on this Site and/or this Policy, at any time without notice. You should regularly review this Policy for any changes. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy on this Site. By continuing to use the Site, you agree to any changes, and by providing continued access to the Site we are providing you consideration for agreement to such changes.

**11\. Children**

We take the protection of children’s privacy seriously. We operate this Site in compliance with all applicable law in the above Jurisdiction. Children under the age referred to below for the appropriate Jurisdiction for the Site should have a parent/guardian’s consent before providing any personal information to the website. We will not, as provided by applicable law, require or request children under this age to provide more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the applicable activity on the Site. If we determine upon collection that a user is under this age, we will not use or maintain his/her personal information without the parent/guardian’s consent. Without such consent, though, the child may not be able to participate in certain activities. However, in certain circumstances, we may maintain and use such information (in accordance with the rest of this Policy and applicable law) in order to notify and obtain consent from the parent/guardian and for certain safety, security, liability and other purposes permitted under applicable law. A parent/ guardian can review, remove, change or refuse further collection or use of their child’s personal information by contacting us as provided above (include child’s name, address and e-mail address).

_Site’s Jurisdiction/Applicable Age:_

  * United States & Australia: Under 13 years of age.
  * Other Jurisdictions: Under 12 years of age.

**12\. Jurisdiction**

We control and operate the Site from the above Company Location (regardless of where hosting servers are located). All matters relating to the Site are governed by the laws of the above Jurisdiction, without reference to conflict or choice of law principles. You agree that jurisdiction and venue for any legal proceeding relating to the Site shall be in appropriate courts located in the above Jurisdiction. We do not warrant or imply that the Site or materials on it are appropriate for use outside of the above Country. The information set forth in this Site concerning any products or services is applicable only in the Jurisdiction and these products or services may not be available in all locations. If you are located outside of this Country, you are solely responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws.

**13\. Transfer of assets**

During the course of our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all or substantially all of our assets, personally and non-personally identifiable information we have collected about the users of the Site may be transferred to such entity. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganisation proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties.

**14\. Severability**

If for any reason, any provision herein is found void or unenforceable, it will be severed to the extent void or unenforceable and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.

**15\. Definitions/Interpretation**

As used herein:

“Damages” means any and all direct, special, indirect, consequential or punitive loss or other damages of any kind (whether in contract, including fundamental breach, tort, including negligence, or otherwise).

“including” means “including, but not limited to”.

“materials sent to the Site” (and “materials you send to the Site” and other like terms) means anything emailed, uploaded, posted or otherwise transmitted or sent to the Site (whether information, text, material, data or code or other) by you or another user.

“Related Parties” means all of our parent, subsidiary and affiliated companies, Site Developers and other promotional partners.

“Site Developer” means any party involved in creating, producing, delivering or maintaining the Site.

“use of this Site” (and “using” and other like terms) means “any and all use of the Site of any kind whatsoever, including access to, browsing of, reviewing, posting of, transmitting, reviewing, downloading, and other using the Site or any material on the Site.”

**16\. Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice, you can contact us at:

www.tassimo.co.uk, Website Manager, Jacobs Douwe Egberts GB Ltd., Horizon, Honey Lane, Hurley, Maidenhead, Berkshire, SL6 6RJ, England.

Alternatively you can call us on 0800 032 8833 (between 9am and 5pm GMT) and we will be happy to assist you with your query or contact us by email using our [contact us form](http://contactus.jdecoffee.com/tassimo-united-kingdom/ "contact us form") .
